<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Lab-protocols on Krause Lab</title>
    <link>https://krauselab.net/lab-protocols/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Lab-protocols on Krause Lab</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy; Diane Krause {year}</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 02 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://krauselab.net/lab-protocols/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>BRD-U Immunohistochemistry on Mouse - Paraffin</title>
      <link>https://krauselab.net/lab-protocols/ihc_brdu_paraffin/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://krauselab.net/lab-protocols/ihc_brdu_paraffin/</guid>
      <description>Antibody - Dako mouse monoclonal clone Bu20, cat# M0744 1. Heat tissues to 60°C for 10 mins 2. Deparaffinize and rehydrate tissue sections through series of xylenes and ethanol incubations a. Xylenes or alternative (Citrisolve, Histoclear) incubate 2 times, 5 min each incubation (2 x 5 min) b. 100% ethanol, 5 min c. 95% ethanol, 5 min d. 70% ethanol, 5 min 3. Rinse the slides once in dH20 4. Wash with PBS for 5 mins 5.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Basic FISH Protocol - Paraffin</title>
      <link>https://krauselab.net/lab-protocols/basic_fish_paraffin/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://krauselab.net/lab-protocols/basic_fish_paraffin/</guid>
      <description>Unless noted otherwise, all incubations take place at room temperature
 Heat tissues to 60°C for 10 mins Deparaffinize and rehydrate tissue sections through series of xylenes and ethanol incubations
a. Xylenes or alternative (Citrisolve, Histoclear) incubate 2 times, 5 min each incubation (2 x 5 min)
b. 100% ethanol, 5 min
c. 95% ethanol, 5 min
d. 70% ethanol, 5 min
 Rinse the slides once in dH20 Wash with PBS for 5 mins Antigen retrieval: Preheat BD retrievagen A solution (BD Pharmigen cat# 550524) in coplin jar in steamer.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CD45 GFP CK immunofluorescence on mouse - paraffin</title>
      <link>https://krauselab.net/lab-protocols/cd45_paraffin/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://krauselab.net/lab-protocols/cd45_paraffin/</guid>
      <description>GFP Antibody - Clontech mouse monoclonal, clone JL-8 cat# 8371-2
Prepare MOM solutions according to manufacturers instructions- Vector MOM Peroxidase kit (cat# PK-2200) or MOM basic kit (cat# BMK-2202). All incubations take place at room temperature unless indicated.
 Heat tissues to 60°C for 10 mins Deparaffinize and rehydrate tissue sections through series of xylenes and ethanol incubations a. Xylenes or alternative (Citrisolve, Histoclear) incubate 2 times, 5 min each incubation (2 x 5 min) b.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>GFP Immunohistochemistry on Mouse - Paraffin</title>
      <link>https://krauselab.net/lab-protocols/gfp_ihc/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://krauselab.net/lab-protocols/gfp_ihc/</guid>
      <description>GFP Antibody - Molecular probes rabbit polyclonal, cat# A11122 Note: works best on lung, variable on other tissues
 Heat tissues to 60°C for 10 mins Deparaffinize and rehydrate tissue sections through series of xylenes and ethanol incubations a. Xylenes or alternative (Citrisolve, Histoclear) incubate 2 times, 5 min each incubation (2 x 5 min) b. 100% ethanol, 5 min c. 5% ethanol, 5 min d. 70% ethanol, 5 min</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Preparing Y-Chromosome Probe</title>
      <link>https://krauselab.net/lab-protocols/preparing-probe/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://krauselab.net/lab-protocols/preparing-probe/</guid>
      <description>Generate Y chromosome template DNA If you are starting with an aliquot of 2-4 µl template DNA, amplify the DNA several (2-3) times by DOP-PCR to generate Y chromosome template. This will be your Y chromosome template stock. Then each time you make probe use DNA from this stock for another batch (8 reaction) DOP-PCR and subsequent labeling. Do not repeatedly amplify DOP-PCR as this can bias the oligos generated by selecting for a subpopulation of oligos that amplify particularly well.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Preparing slides for FISH</title>
      <link>https://krauselab.net/lab-protocols/preparing-slides/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://krauselab.net/lab-protocols/preparing-slides/</guid>
      <description>Protocol for preparation of slides with bone marrow or peripheral blood for fluorescence in situ hybridization</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Basic FISH Protocol - Frozen</title>
      <link>https://krauselab.net/lab-protocols/basic_fish_frozen/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://krauselab.net/lab-protocols/basic_fish_frozen/</guid>
      <description>Unless noted otherwise, all incubations take place at room temperature
 Equilibrate frozen sections to RT Wash in 2xSSC, incubate two times, 3 min each incubation (2x3min) Incubate in 0.2 M HCL for 10 min at room temperature Wash in 2xSSC 2x3min Incubate in 1M NaSCN for 20 min at 75-80°C Wash in 2xSSC 2x3min Water rinse Ethanol dehydrate (70%, 95%, 100%), 1 min each Air-dry slides Hybridization: pre-heat probe to 75°C, vortex to mix</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>